International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records 5535
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Teamsters Local 99 (Rochester, N.Y.) Records
1957-1972
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
5535
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Records of Local 99, the Rochester, New York Cannery Local of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
3338522
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 01, 2007
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Scope and Contents
Records of Local 99, the Rochester, New York Cannery Local of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Materials are arranged chronologically, and alphabetically by subject thereunder.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5308: Emergency Board no. 52 Files 5404 mf: Raymond W. Bergan Teamsters-Monitor Litigation in the Court of Appeals on Microfilm 5865: International Brotherhood of Teamsters National Master Freight Agreements Additional 6317/008 PUBS: Kheel Center Triangle Fire Centennial Commemoration Collection International Brotherhood of Teamsters, City Employees Union Local 237 Publications
Labor unions -- New York (State) -- Rochester; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America.; International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America. Local 99 (Rochester, N.Y.)
3338522
- Contributions, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Cornell University, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence from members [folder 1 of 2], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence from members [folder 2 of 2], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Deaths, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Election, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Financial Reports, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 12 of 12], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Insurance, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- International Union [folder 1 of 3], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- International Union [folder 2 of 3], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- International Union [folder 3 of 3], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- N.L.R.B. and U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- New York State Dept. of Labor, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Notices, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 1 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 2 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 3 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 4 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 5 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 6 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 7 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 8 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Quaker Maid Division [folder 9 of 9], 1957 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Tax Forms, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Audit, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Baseball Team, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- By-Laws, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Correspondence to & from members [folder 1 of 2], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Correspondence to & from members [folder 2 of 2], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Deaths, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- ECT - Cannery Policy Meeting, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Financial Reports, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 11], 1958 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Insurance, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Insurance Survey, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Arbitration, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Audit, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bonding, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Bureau of National Affairs, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Cannery Policy Committee, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Carges, Henry- Trustee, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Christmas Card mailing list, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Clambake, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Contributions, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 1 of 2], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 2 of 2], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Deaths, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Deyaeger, Alphonse- Recording Secretary, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Eastern Conference, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Eusebio Correa- Trustee, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Financial Reports, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 12 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 13 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 14 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 15 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 16 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 17 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 18 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 19 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 20 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 21 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 22 of 22], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Insurance, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- International Union, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Kennedy-Ervin Bill, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Mailing List, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Mediation Agencies, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Meeting, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Merritt Elwell- Trustee, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- New York State. Dept. of Labor, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- N.Y.S. Unemployment Insurance, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Payroll Records, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Photographs, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Piedmonte, Anthony J. - President, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Quaker Maid [folder 1 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Quaker Maid [folder 2 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Quaker Maid [folder 3 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Quaker Maid [folder 4 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Quaker Maid [folder 5 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Quaker Maid [folder 6 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Quaker Maid [folder 7 of 7], 1959 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Registered members, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Returned mail sent to members, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Saile, Charles - Vice President, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Smith, J. Hungerford Co., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- State Insurance Fund, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Stewards, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Tax Forms, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Withdrawals and Transfers mailed, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Bibles, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Bonding, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Buffet Dinner Dance, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 1 of 2], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 2 of 2], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Deaths, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Disability Benefits, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Donations, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Financial Report, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Insurance, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 1 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 2 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 3 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 4 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Kenny, Thomas J., 1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Meeting Notices, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- N.Y.S. Dept. of Labor, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Notices, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Officers Meeting, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Quaker Maid [folder 1 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Quaker Maid [folder 2 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Quaker Maid [folder 3 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Quaker Maid [folder 4 of 4], 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Retired members, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Tax Forms, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Audit Reports, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- By-laws amendments, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Bonding, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Compensation, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Correspondence to and from members [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Deaths, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Disability, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Donations, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Financial Report, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 12 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 13 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 14 of 14], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Insurance, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 1 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 2 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Int'l. Brotherhood of Teamsters [folder 3 of 3], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Kenny, Thomas J. [folder 1 of 2], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Kenny, Thomas J. [folder 2 of 2], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Ledger Numbers, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Local Union Election, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Mailing lists, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Meeting Notices, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Officer Meeting, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 1 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 2 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 3 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 4 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 5 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Quaker Maid Co. [folder 6 of 6], 1964 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Retired members, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Returned mail sent to members, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Strikes, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Taxes, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Transfers, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Application for Teamsters, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Audit, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Bibles, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Birds Eye, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Blue Cross & Blue Shield, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Bonding [folder 1 of 2], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Bonding [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Buffet Dinner Dance, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Bulletin Board Notices, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- By-laws, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Compensation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Correspondence to and from members, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 1 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 2 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 3 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 4 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Curtice-Burns Co. [folder 5 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Deaths, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Disability, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Donations, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Financial Report, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Grievance, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Insurance, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- International [folder 1 of 2], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- International [folder 2 of 2], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Kenny, T.J., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Legislation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Local Union, Vending, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Monthly Meeting Notices, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Officers Business, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Political Action, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Quaker Maid [folder 1 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Quaker Maid [folder 2 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Quaker Maid [folder 3 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Quaker Maid [folder 4 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Quaker Maid [folder 5 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Quaker Maid [folder 6 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Quaker Maid [folder 7 of 7], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Retired members, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Returned mail, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Tax Bureau [folder 1 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Tax Bureau [folder 2 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Tax Bureau [folder 3 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Tax Bureau [folder 4 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Tax Bureau [folder 5 of 5], 1965 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Telegrams, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Transfers, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 1 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 2 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 3 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 4 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 5 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 6 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- A & P Tea Co. [folder 7 of 7], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Arbitration, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Audit, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Authorization Slips, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Bibles, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Birds Eye [folder 1 of 5], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Birds Eye [folder 2 of 5], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Birds Eye [folder 3 of 5], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Birds Eye [folder 4 of 5], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Birds Eye [folder 5 of 5], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Blue Cross - Blue Shield, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Bonding, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Buffet Dinner Dance, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Convention Material, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 1 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 2 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 3 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 4 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 5 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 6 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 7 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Curtice-Burns [folder 8 of 8], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Donation, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Equal Pay Law Compliance, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Fair Labor Laws, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Financial Statement, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 11], 1966 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Grievances, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Internal Revenue Service, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- International Convention, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- International Union, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Kenny, T.J., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Legislation, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Mailing list, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Medicare, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Monthly Meeting Notices, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- N.Y. Board of Mediation, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- N.Y.S. Unemployment Insurance, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Old Business, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- State Insurance Fund (N.Y.), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Steward's File, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Tax Forms, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Telegrams, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Arbitrations, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 1 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 2 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 3 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 4 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 5 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 6 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 7 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co. [folder 8 of 8], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Audit, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Authorization Slips, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Bibles, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Birds Eye [folder 1 of 5], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Birds Eye [folder 2 of 5], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Birds Eye [folder 3 of 5], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Birds Eye [folder 4 of 5], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Birds Eye [folder 5 of 5], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Blue Cross - Blue Shield, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Buffet Dinner Dance, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- By-laws, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Cannery Policy & Committee Meetings, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 1 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 2 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 3 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 4 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 5 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 6 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 7 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 8 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 9 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 10 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 11 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 12 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 13 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Curtice-Burns, Inc. [folder 14 of 14], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Donations, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Equal Pay Law [folder 1 of 2], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Equal Pay Law [folder 2 of 2], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Fair Labor Laws, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Financial Statements, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 1 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 2 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 3 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 4 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 5 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 6 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 7 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 8 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 9 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 10 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 11 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Gerber Products Co. [folder 12 of 12], 1967 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Grievances, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Internal Revenue Service, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- International Union, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Kenny, T.J., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Labor-Management Disclosure Act, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Legislation, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Mailing list, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Medicare, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Merger Locals 99, 300, 791, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Monthly Meetings Notices, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- New Business, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 66)
- N.Y.S. Board of Mediation, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 67)
- N.Y.S. Tax Forms, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Old Business, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 69)
- Out of Work Benefits, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Pension Fund, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 71)
- Political Correspondence, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 72)
- Post Office Check Guarantee, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 73)
- Refund of Stewards' Dues, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 74)
- Request of Relief Dues, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 75)
- State Insurance Fund (N.Y.), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 76)
- Stewards File, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 77)
- Unemployment Insurance (N.Y.S.), 1967 (Box 7, Folder 78)